Let's talk about the brokerage report.
Vamakshi has joined us
with complete details. Vanshi, good morning. Tell us. Yes, let's
start
with ICC Prudential. We are looking at the
report from them and they have highlighted
that the company has recorded 12% premium growth in the month of June, which is the
highest level in the last 13 months.
Distribution efficiency is improving
and due to this, Jeffers has
maintained the buy opinion and increased its target
price from ₹640 to ₹700.
Apart from this, we will be keeping an eye
on United Spirits. There is a
report from Quality. Karnataka taxi growth may
take off tomorrow and due to this high, the
consumer may get around 14 to
15% high.
Overall, they believe that all the
brands present in Karnataka will
want to adjust their pricing strategy because they will have to offset these higher
taxis. So overall, all these
Due to updates,
lion and finally we will focus
on delivery. We are seeing that
there is a report from MK and it is highlighting
that India's e-commerce shipment market can
double by 2026. In fact, they are
expecting revenue of 24%.
From 2023 to 2026, there are
expectations of adjusted margin of 7.8% and pattern around
is also expected. In 2026, the
cost of transportation of delivery in B to C
express segment is
around 20% less than its computer counterpart. And in fact, the
structure and growth story of India's largest space,
delivery is a
good opportunity in it. Therefore, due to this,
MK has started coverage with delivery and has
given a target price of 465.
Thank you for all these details now.